jaxenter.com 2019-08-14

# Privacy Policy - JAXenter

**1 General Information**

We are pleased about your visit on our website “JAXenter.com”. The protection and security of our customers’ and users’ data is important to us. We have therefore designed our website and our business processes in such a way that as little personal data as possible is collected or processed. The following privacy policy explains which information we collect during your visit to our website and which parts of this information may be used in which way.

**2 Server Logs**

When visiting our website, our web server, like any other web server, stores standardized information about your device and the browser used in a log file. We process this data in order to analyse errors on our server and attempts at misuse. In detail, the IP address, the specific address of the page visited by you, if applicable the page from which you reached us (link source), the transmitted identification of the browser, as well as system date and time of the page visit are recorded here. We are not able to link this data to a person unless you provide more information about yourself in one of the forms provided. This is the case, for example, if you register for one of our seminars or subscribe to our newsletter. Even in these cases, we store the data in separate systems and only merge them in exceptional cases (attempted misuse). The legal basis for this data processing is our legitimate interest.

**3 Technical provisioning – Cookies**

“Cookies” are used on our site. These simplify and accelerate the provisioning of your visit to our website or are necessary to enable you to use our website. If you do not wish our website to store cookies on your computer, you can deactivate the cookie feature in your browser settings or adjust the settings so that you are informed when cookies are used on a website.

**4 Retargeting**

On our website we use retargeting technology. We use retargeting to categorize website visitors into user groups. Depending on the respective user group, we address website visitors on other websites or in apps with personalized advertising about our products and services. The legal basis for this data processing is our legitimate interest.  
We use the following products, which are provided to us by service providers:

**4.1 “Facebook Custom Audience” / “Facebook Pixel”**

“Facebook Custom Audience” and “Facebook Pixel” are products of Facebook Ireland Ltd, Hanover Reach, 5-7 Hanover Quay, Dublin 2, Ireland (“Facebook”). Our website uses a “Facebook Pixel” by Facebook, which establishes a direct connection to the Facebook servers. The Facebook server receives information about your visit on our webite. Facebook will link this information with your personal Facebook account if you have such an account and are logged in. If you visit other websites that also use “Facebook Custom Audience” / “Facebook Pixel”, this information will also be linked to your user account. However, we do not know which other websites you visit. If you are not logged in to Facebook or are not a Facebook user while visiting our website, your website visit will not be linked to a Facebook user account.

For more information about Facebook’s privacy settings, please see Facebook’s privacy policy at <https://www.facebook.com/about/privacy/>. Specifically, what content and information you have shared through your use of Facebook, you can manage through the “Activity Log” tool or download through the “Download Your Data” tool on Facebook.

**4.2 Twitter “Website Tag for Remarketing”**

“Website Tag for Remarketing” is a product of Twitter International Company, One Cumberland Place, Fenian Street, Dublin 2, D02 AX07, Ireland (“Twitter”), which establishes a direct connection to Twitter servers. The Twitter server receives information about your visit on our webite. Twitter links this information to a unique ID that is stored on your device in the form of a cookie or provided by your device (“advertising ID” on smartphones). If you visit other websites that also use ” Website Tag for Remarketing “, this information will also be linked with your unique ID. However, we do not know which other websites you visit.

For more information on how Twitter protects your privacy, please see Twitter’s privacy policy at <https://twitter.com/personalization>.

**4.3 LinkedIn “Insight Tag”**

“Insight Tag” is a product of LinkedIn Ireland Unlimited Company, Wilton Plaza, Wilton Place, Dublin 2, Ireland (“LinkedIn”). Our website uses a pixel provided by LinkedIn that establishes a direct connection to the LinkedIn servers. The LinkedIn server receives information about your visit on our webite. LinkedIn links this information to a unique ID that is stored on your device in the form of a cookie or provided by your device (“advertising ID” on smartphones). or with your LinkedIn account, if you are logged in. If you visit other websites that also use “Insight Tag”, this information will also be linked to your unique ID or your account. However, we do not know which other websites you visit.

For more information on how LinkedIn protects your privacy, please see LinkedIn’s privacy policy at [https://www.LinkedIn.com/psettings/](https://www.linkedin.com/psettings/).

**5 Statistical analysis – tracking**

We use tracking technology on our website to measure, evaluate and optimize our website content. To protect our users and partners, we can also identify and defend ourselves against fraud and security risks. The legal basis for this data processing is our legitimate interest.

**5.1 “Google Analytics”**

We use Google Analytics, a web analysis service of Google Ireland Ltd, Gordon House, Barrow Street, Dublin 4 Ireland (“Google”) The protection of your data is important to us, therefore we have configured Google Analytics to use the configuration parameter “anonymizeIp”. By this, your IP address will be shortened and never processed fully. We therefore process your personal usage data anonymously. It is not possible for us to draw any conclusions about your identity.

For more information on how Google protects your privacy, please see the information at <http://www.google.com/analytics/terms/en.html> and <https://www.google.de/intl/en/policies/>.

**5.2 “Google Universal Analytics” / “Google Global Site Tag”**

We use “Google Universal Analytics”/ “Google Global Site Tag”. We use both tools to gather information about the use of our services across different devices. For this purpose, we store a unique ID on your device.  
You may opt-out from this data processing at any time by visiting you Google Account settings and turning off cross-device user analysis

Further information about Google Universal Analytics can be found here: <https://support.google.com/analytics/answer/2838718>

**5.3 “Google Adwords Conversion Tracking”**

We use Google Adwords Conversion Tracking to track interaction with ads booked by us. With this service we analyse the total number of users who clicked on one of our ads and were forwarded to a page defined by us. We do not receive any information that per-sonally identifies users.

**5.4 “Facebook Conversion Tracking”**

We use Facebook Conversion Tracking to track how many people are interacting with our advertisements and which Facebook advertisement has led to a conversion. Facebook will link this information with your personal Facebook account if you have such an account and are logged in. If you visit other websites that also use Facebook Conversion Tracking, this information will also be linked to your user account. However, we do not know which other websites you visit. If you are not logged in to Facebook or are not a Facebook user while visiting our website, your website visit will not be assigned to a Facebook user account.

**5.5  “Twitter Analytics”**

We also use Twitter Analytics to track your interaction with our website and analyse data about it to improve our services.

**6 Newsletter**

You can subscribe to one of our newsletters on our website. If you provide information about yourself on the registration form, this information will only be processed based on your consent. You can revoke your consent at any time with effect for the future.

**7 Opt-Out for remarketing and tracking**

You may opt-out from the use of retargeting and tracking tools on our website at any time. Please click on the following link to do so:

Opt-Out for all remarketing and tracking tools.

After clicking the link, we store an opt-out cookie with an unlimited validity on your device. If you use our website with multiple devices you must opt-out from the use of retargeting and tracking tools for each device separately, as we cannot assign multiple devices to individual visitors. After your opt-out, no third party tools will be embedded into our website and these third party providers will not receive data about your visit.

**8 Further Information / contact**

If you have any further questions, e.g. about data we have stored about you, please do not hesitate to contact us.  
Software & Support Media GmbH, Schwedlerstr. 8,60314 Frankfurt, Germany is the controller according to data protection law. Contact requests may be sent via email to [info@sandsmedia.com](mailto:info@sandsmedia.com).

Mrs Sabrina Brameshuber – Bitkom Servicegesellschaft mbH, Albrechtstraße 10, 10117 Berlin, Germany is our Data Protection Officer. Contact requests may be sent via email to [datenschutz@bitkom-consult.de](mailto:datenschutz@bitkom-consult.de).
